(Man:)Uh, we're gonna get started
in a couple minutes. Enjoy.
(Leonard:)Who are you texting?
(Howard:)Raj. He really wants
to see this movie.
Oh, he'll never
make it in time.
(Leonard:)I know.
I want to make him feel bad.
"Ha, ha. Leonard and I are
about to see Suicide Squad.
Spoiler alert: when I see you
I'm gonna spoil it."
(Leonard:)You're a good friend.
(chuckles)
(phone chimes)
Okay. (clears throat)
(Raj(at the workshop):)Would you ladies please
leave the room for a moment?
(Penny:)Why?
(Raj:)I need to rub my genitals
on their prototype.
(Bernadette:)What's going on?
(Raj:)Leonard and Howard
don't have a flat.
(Raj:)They went to the movies. Look.
(Bernadette:)Son of a bitch.
Un-freakin' believable.
(Raj:)Oh. You know what?
I'm gonna let them know
(Raj:)that I'm here with you
and that they're busted.
(Penny:)No. You know what? Don't. Don't.